Okay so one of the things you want to work on is the coming in and out of the front door that is typically where the dog are loose in the house when you are not home.
When you come in to the house that is typically where you are going to be greeted by your dogs.
We are going to do this 2 ways I'm going to show you how chaotic it could be if we do it with multiple dogs and then we are going to do it again with just one dog.
So I'm going to go out the door and then I'm going to come in as if I'm coming home.
Hey guys how are doing?
Hey pups how are doing?
Off.
Hey how are doing?
Hi guys how are doing?
Good alright so what we did is in this case it was just the baby that jump and then I immediately then walk out off the house and came back again and rewarded here for not jumping.
So we are going to do it again with just one dog Ty we would use you, Ursula, Raven come over here now we are going to do it with one dog.
Hey Ty how are doing? Hey buddy come over here hi what a good boy, yes good job, good boy. So as you can see it is a little bit less chaotic when you are working with one dog at a time and working at the doors we are kind of combining 2 things here and talking about working with multiple dogs and the benefits with working with one dog at a time.
But also working with come into the door and what kind of greeting you want to have from your dog when you come into the house.